Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
5488 B
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
669 linear feet.
Correspondence, Rule books, Agreements, etc.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
SUBJECTS
Names:
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
Subjects:
Railroads--Employees--Labor unions--United States--Sources.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted. Please contact the Kheel Center Reference Archivist for access information.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
This forms a portion of collection #5488 B. The guide to the entire collection is available here.
Series CI is arranged in 9 sub-series by Union file number.
Series CII is arranged in 8 sub-series by Union file number.
Series CIII is arranged in 2 sub-series by Union file number.
CONTAINER LIST
- Series CI. 1951 CONVENTION
  - Sub-Series 501-0. 1951 Convention. San Francisco, California
    - General, 1951-1953 (Box 616, Folder 1)
      May 11, 1951-53.
    - General, 1951 (Box 616, Folder 2)
      April 1951-May 10, 1951.
    - General, 1948-1951 (Box 616, Folder 3)
      1948-March 1951.
  - Sub-Series 501-1. 1951 Convention. Resolutions
    - General, 1950-1956 (Box 616, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 501-2. 1951 Convention. Appointments
    - General, 1950-1951 (Box 616, Folder 5)
    - General, 1950-1951 (Box 616, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 501-3. 1951 Convention. Amendments to Grand Lodge Constitution, Statutes for the Government of Lodges and Protective Laws of the Brotherhood
    - General, 1950-1951 (Box 616, Folder 7)
    - Report of the Committee on Grand Lodge Constitution and Laws of the Brotherhood, 1951 (Box 616, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 501-4. 1951 Convention. Transportation. Pullman Rates
    - General, 1951 (Box 617, Folder 1)
      June 20, 1951-December 1951.
    - General, 1951 (Box 617, Folder 2)
      June 6-, 1951.
    - General, 1951 (Box 617, Folder 3)
      March 1951-June 5, 1951.
    - Duplicate Refund Forms. A-B, 1951 (Box 617, Folder 4)
    - Duplicate Refund Forms. C-D, 1951 (Box 617, Folder 5)
    - Duplicate Refund Forms. E-G, 1951 (Box 617, Folder 6)
    - Duplicate Refund Forms. H-K, 1951 (Box 617, Folder 7)
    - Duplicate Refund Forms. L-M, 1951 (Box 617, Folder 8)
    - Duplicate Refund Forms. N-R, 1951 (Box 617, Folder 9)
    - Duplicate Refund Forms. S-T, 1951 (Box 617, Folder 10)
    - Duplicate Refund Forms. U-Z, 1951 (Box 617, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 501-5. 1951 Convention. Speakers
    - General, 1951 (Box 617, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 501-6. 1951 Convention. Grand President's Report
    - General, 1947-1952 (Box 617, Folder 13)
    - General, 1951 (Box 617, Folder 14-18)
  - Sub-Series 501-7. 1951 Convention. Appeals
    - General, 1951 (Box 617, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 501-8. 1951 Convention. Mileage and Per Diem
    - General, 1951 (Box 617, Folder 20)
- Series CII. UNITED STATES DEPARTMENT OF STATE
  - Sub-Series 504-0. United States Department of State. General
    - General, 1954-1959 (Box 618a, Folder 1)
      November 1954-59.
    - General, 1952-1954 (Box 618a, Folder 2)
      June 1952-October 1954.
    - General, 1951-1952 (Box 618a, Folder 3)
      1951-May 1952.
    - General, 1950 (Box 618a, Folder 4)
      February-December 1950.
    - General, 1949-1950 (Box 618a, Folder 5)
      October 1949-January 1950.
    - General, 1948-1949 (Box 618a, Folder 6)
      1948-September 1949.
    - General, 1949 (Box 618a, Folder 7)
      March 17-18, 1949.
  - Sub-Series 504-1. United States Department of State. Inter-American Economic Conference
    - International Conference of American States, Bogota, Colombia, 1948 (Box 618a, Folder 8)
      March 30, 1948-May 2, 1948.
    - General, 1948-1949 (Box 618a, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 504-2. United States Department of State. North Atlantic Treaty Organization
    - General, 1949-1962 (Box 618b, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 504-3. United States Department of State. Publications
    - General, 1954-1955 (Box 618b, Folder 2)
    - General, 1951-1953 (Box 618b, Folder 3)
    - General, 1950 (Box 618b, Folder 4)
      September 24, 1950-December 1950.
    - General, 1950 (Box 618b, Folder 5)
      April 1950-September 23, 1950.
    - General, 1949-1950 (Box 618b, Folder 6)
      September 22, 1949-March 1950.
    - General, 1949 (Box 618b, Folder 7)
      January 1949-September 22, 1949.
  - Sub-Series 504-4. United States Department of State. Military Assistance Program
    - General, 1949 (Box 618b, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 504-5. United States Department of State. Cooperative Technical Assistance Point 4
    - General, 1949-1954 (Box 618b, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 504-6. United States Department of State. International Trade Organization
    - General, 1950 (Box 618b, Folder 10)
      July-November 1950.
    - General, 1949-1950 (Box 618b, Folder 11)
      1949-October 1950.
  - Sub-Series 504-7. United States Department of State. Mutual Security Program
    - General, 1954 (Box 619, Folder 1)
    - General, 1953 (Box 619, Folder 2)
      May-December 1953.
    - General, 1951-1953 (Box 619, Folder 3)
      1951-April 1953.
- Series CIII. INTERNATIONAL CONFEDERATION OF FREE TRADE UNIONS
  - Sub-Series 505-0. International Confederation of Free Trade Unions
    - General. News Bulletin, 1955-1964 (Box 619, Folder 4)
    - General, 1955-1959 (Box 619, Folder 5)
    - General, 1960-1961 (Box 619, Folder 6)
      1960-July 1961.
    - General, 1952-1954 (Box 619, Folder 7)
      June 1952-54.
    - General, 1951-1952 (Box 619, Folder 8)
      August 1951-May 1952.
    - General, 1953-1954 (Box 619, Folder 9)
    - General. Report of First General Council Meeting, 1952 (Box 619, Folder 10)
      July 1-5, 1952.
    - General. News Bulletin, 1951-1952 (Box 619, Folder 11)
    - General, 1951 (Box 619, Folder 12)
      1951 July
    - General, 1949-1951 (Box 620, Folder 1)
      December 11, 1949-June 1951.
    - General, 1949 (Box 620, Folder 2)
      March 1949-November 25, 1949.
    - General, 1949 (Box 620, Folder 3)
      November 26, 1949-December 10, 1949.
  - Sub-Series 505-1. International Confederation of Free Trade Unions
    - Pan-American Railway Congress, 1952-1957 (Box 620, Folder 4)